http://www.slingsby.com/privacy-policy.htm

Ladders & Steps
Ladders
Heavy duty laddersLadder AccessoriesLoft LaddersPush Up LaddersRope Operated LaddersSingle Section LaddersSpecialist Ladders
Work Stations And Platforms
Fixed Work Stations And PlatformsMobile Workstations And Platforms
New Ladders & Steps ProductsLadders & Steps ClearanceClearance
Waste & Recycling
Ash Trays & Cigarette Bins
Ash & Litter BinsAsh Only Bins
Clinical Waste Disposal
Clinical Waste LabelsMobile Clinical Waste BinsStatic Clinical Waste Bins
Indoor Litterbins
Fire Retardant Indoor Litter BinsGeneral Purpose Indoor Litter Bins
Indoor Sackholders
Fire Retardant Indoor SackholdersGeneral Purpose Indoor Sackholders
Outdoor Litterbins
Hooded Outdoor Litter BinsOpen Top Outdoor Litter BinsOutdoor Dustbins & AccessoriesOutdoor Wheelie Bins & AccessoriesWall & Post Mounted Outdoor Litter Bins
Outdoor Sackholders
Recycling & Confidential Waste Bins
Confidential Waste BinsRecycling Waste BinsWaste Compactors
Waste Sacks & AccessoriesWaste Transport & Storage
Waste Storage ProductsWaste Transport
New Waste & Recycling ProductsWaste & Recycling ClearanceClearance
Flooring & Matting
Floor TilesFloor Treatments
Floor CoatingsFloor maintenance
Matting & Accessories
Anti-Fatigue MattingAnti-viral MattingChair MatsEntrance MattingMessage logo mattingSlip Resistant MattingSpecialist Matting & Accessories
Slip Resistant Floor Tapes
General Purpose Slip Resistant Floor TapesPhotoluminescent Slip Resistant Floor TapesPrinted Slip Resistant Floor Tapes
Stair Treads & NosingsWalkways/GratingsNew Flooring & Matting ProductsFlooring & Matting ClearanceClearance
Handling & Lifting
Barrows & Tilt Trucks
Balanced General Purpose TrucksTipping CartsWheelbarrows
Container & Shelf Trolleys
Container TrolleysPlastic Shelf TrolleysStainless Shelf TrolleysSteel Shelf TrolleysTimber Shelf Trolleys
Container Trucks
Aluminium Container TrucksLinen Container TrucksPlastic Container TrucksSteel Container TrucksTimber Container TrucksWire Container Trucks
Conveyors
Roller Wheel Gravity Conveyors
Cylinder Handling
Cylinder TrolleysCylinder Storage
Diy Trolleys & Board Carriers
Board CarriersDiy Trolleys
Dollies & Skates
DolliesSkates
Drum Handling
Drum Clamps Positioners & TiltersDrum Handling AccessoriesDrum SlingsDrum StandsDrum Trucks
Handtrucks
Folding HandtrucksMultifunction HandtrucksSpecialist HandtrucksStairclimbing HandtrucksStandard Handtrucks
Lift Tables & Pallet Trucks
High Lift Pallet TrucksLift TablesPallet TrucksStackersWork Positioners
Lifting Gear & Load Restraint
Cranes & Crane ArmsFork AttachmentsGantriesHoists Clamps & Girder TrolleysLifting Fittings & SlingsLoad RestraintSuction Cups & Winches
Platform Trucks Tugs & Trailers
Platform TrucksPowered TugsTrailers
Roll Containers & Covers
Demountable Roll ContainersNestable A Frame Roll ContainersPlastic Based Roll Containers
Pumps
Air Operated PumpsElectrically Operated PumpsEngine driven pumpsLubrication EquipmentManual PumpsPump AccessoriesSprayers
Skips
Bottom Hinged SkipsTipping Skips
New Handling & Lifting ProductsHandling & Lifting ClearanceClearance
Cleaning & Hygiene
Cleaning Materials
Cleaning Cloths & SpongesCleaning Fluid DispensersCleaning Fluids & Sprays
Floorcare
Cleaning StationsFloor ScrubbersMopping ProductsSweeping ProductsVacuum Cleaners
Cleaning Safety Signs
A-Board Cleaning Safety SignsBarrier System Cleaning Safety SignsCone System Cleaning Safety Signs
Pressure Washers
Cold Water Pressure WashersHot Water Pressure Washers
Steam CleanersStreet Cleaning
Litter PickersStreet Cleaning Carts & Accessories
Trolleys & Storage
Cleaning StorageCleaning TrolleysLaundry Trolleys
Washroom
Baby ChangingHand DryersOdour Control SystemsUrinal Maintenance ProductsWashroom Dispensers & ConsumablesWashroom bins
Window CleaningNew Cleaning & Hygiene ProductsClearanceCleaning & Hygiene Clearance
Mailroom & Packaging
Bubblewrap Foam & Polythene Packaging
BubblewrapPackaging FoamPolythene BagsPolythene SheetingPolythene Tubing
Cardboard & Paper Packaging & Accessories
AccessoriesCartonsMailing BoxesPostal TubesProtective Paper Packaging & Dispensers
Glue Guns & Dispensers
Glue GunsGlue Sticks
Heat SealersKnives & Scissors
Cutting AccessoriesKnives
Labels Pouches & DispensersMail Sacks & Sack HoldersMailing Pouches & Envelopes
EnvelopesSecure External Mailing PouchesSecurity Seals For Pouches And Sacks
Mailroom & Packing Furniture
Mailroom BenchesMailroom MachinesMailroom SortersPacking BenchesPost Boxes
Mailroom Scales
Mailroom Parcel Scales
Mailroom Trolleys
Manual Mailroom TrolleysPowered Mailroom Trolleys
Shrinkwrap & Stretchwrap
Polythene Shrinkwrap FilmShrinkwrap Dispensers & TrolleysShrinkwrap GunsShrinkwrap KitsStretchwrap & Dispensers
Staplers Nailers & AccessoriesTapes & Dispensers
Tape DispensersTapes
Tying Materials
Rope & Twine
Strapping & Strapping Tools
Buckles, Seals & AccessoriesStrappingStrapping DispensersStrapping KitsStrapping MachinesStrapping Tools
New Mailroom & Packaging ProductsClearanceMailroom & Packaging Clearance
Office
Audio Visual Equipment
Audio Visual Trolleys & CabinetsProjection ScreensProjectorsLecterns
Exhibition & Literature Display
Display Panel SystemsExhibition DisplayLiterature DispensersPoster Display Frames
Flipcharts Whiteboards & Accessories
Combination UnitsFlipchart & Whiteboard AccessoriesFlipchartsWhiteboards
Furniture
Acoustic ScreensChairs & SeatingDesking & AccessoriesOffice LightingProtection screens and dividersRangesStorageTablesTrolleys
Home officeNoticeboards & Accessories
External NoticeboardsInternal Noticeboards
Office Machines
Cash Registers & RollsComb BindersCutters & TrimmersLabelling MachinesLaminatorsShredders
Office DeskTop EssentialsStorage Boxes
Archive BoxesBox FilesGeneral Purpose Boxes
Time Management & Planning
Clocking SystemsClocks & TimersIn/Out BoardsPlanning Boards
New Office ProductsClearanceOffice Clearance
Premises
Barriers
Barrier TapesBollardsChain BarriersFolding BarriersProtective BarriersRetractable BarriersRope Barriers
Catering Equipment
Catering AppliancesCatering Consumables & SuppliesCatering TrolleysKitchen HardwareWater Coolers & Accessories
Communication
Public Address EquipmentTelephone EquipmentTwo Way Radio Systems
Cycle Storage
Cycle LockersCycle Racks & StandsCycle Shelters
Dock Equipment
Dock & Vehicle BumpersDock LightsDock PlatesRopes & TarpaulinsWheel Chocks
Environmental Control
Air Conditioners & CoolersAir purifiersDehumidifiers & DryersFansHeatersThermometers
Flags & Event Equipment
Event TentsFlag PostsFlagsStaging
Flood ProtectionGrit Bins & Salt Spreaders
De-Icing ProductsSalt & GritSalt & Grit BinsSalt SpreadersSnow PloughsSnow Tools
Indoor Furniture
Chairs & SeatingFurniture Transport TrolleysTable & Chair Combination UnitsTables
Outdoor & Street Furniture
External DisplayPlantersSeating & Tables
Parks & Garden Equipment
Parks & Garden Storage
Pest Control
Bird SpikesFlying Insect KillerPest Baiting StationsPest RepellentPest Traps
Post BoxesPartitioning & Cubicles
CubiclesPartitioning
Pvc Door Systems & Wall/Door Protection
Cabinet, Wall & Door ProtectionPvc & Rubber Door System
Ramps & Disability Products
Disability Assistant ProductsRampsWheelchairs
Safety Rails
Fibreglass Safety RailsSteel Safety Rails
Smoking/Vaping SheltersTraffic Management
Cable ProtectionGatehousesImpact ProtectionPremises Entrance BarriersSpeed Restriction
Window FilmsPremises ClearanceNew Premises ProductsClearance
Lockers & Cloakroom
Cloak & Changing Room Equipment
Changing Room BenchesCoat Rails & HooksCoat StandsGarment RailsHangersLaundry EquipmentUmbrella Stands
Lockers
Cube LockersLocker AccessoriesPlastic LockersSee through lockersSpecialist lockersStandard lockers
New Lockers & Cloakroom ProductsLockers & Cloakroom ClearanceClearance
Safety & Security
Cash Handling
Cash Security ProductsCoin Counters
CCTV camerasDoor SecurityFire Safety Equipment
Fire AlertFire FightingFire PointsFire Safety Accessories
First Aid & Medical Room
First Aid CabinetsFirst Aid Consumables & KitsFirst Aid FridgesFirst Aid LiteratureFirst Aid SignsFirst aid stationsMedical Room FurniturePatient HandlingShowers & Eye Wash Stations
Flood Protection
Hazardous Substance Storage
Acid & Alkali StorageFlammable Liquid StoragePesticide & Agrochemical Storage
Key Security Systems
Access controlKey CabinetsSelf-Retracting Keyreels
Line & Road Marking
Line Marking ApplicatorsLine Marking PaintLine Marking TapeStencils
Lockout ProductsMirrors
Specialist MirrorsSurveillance MirrorsTraffic Safety Mirrors
Padlocks & Seals
Cables & ChainsLocks & HaspsSecurity Seals
Personal Security & Property Marking
Personal AlarmsPersonal SecurityProperty Marking
Safes
Fire SafesSecurity Safes
Safety Barrier Systems
Crowd Control BarriersMachine Safety BarriersMaintenance Safety BarriersProtective Safety BarriersRoad Safety BarriersSafety Tapes
Security CagesSite Security
Anti-Climb SystemsFencing & Accessories
Spill Response Systems
Chemical Spill Response SystemsOil Spill Response SystemsUniversal Spill Response Systems
Traffic Management
Dash CamEntrance BarriersSafety Road SignsSecurity PostsTraffic ConesWheel Clamps
Water Safety EquipmentNew Safety & Security ProductsSafety & Security ClearanceClearance
PPE & Workwear
Ear ProtectionEye ProtectionFace Protection
Fall ArrestFoot Protection
Ladies Foot ProtectionMens Foot ProtectionUnisex Foot Protection
Hand Protection
Head ProtectionPPE storage lockersRespiratory Protection
Respiratory Protection AccessoriesDisposable RespiratorsProtection screensRe-Usable Respirators
Safety Clothing & Workwear
New PPE & Workwear ProductsPPE & Workwear ClearanceClearance
Signs & Labels
AccessoriesAsset Marking Labels
Self Laminating Matt White Vinyl Labels
Disability Discrimination Act Dda Products
Standard Disability Discrimination Act (Dda) SignsTactile Disability Discrimiation Act (Dda) Signs
General Signs Notices & Labels
Asbestos Safety LabelsBar & Restaurant SignsChildrens Play AreasDoor Handle SignsDoor SlidersGeneral NoticesInformation SignsRecycling And Energy Saving SignsSmoking Signs
Hazardous Substance Signs & Labels
Package MarkingVehicle Marking
Pipeline & Valve Marking & Identification
Valve Marking Tags
Quality Labels
Standard Quality LabelsWrite-On Quality Labels
Safety & Quality Tags
Double Sided Safety TagsGeneral tags
Safety Posters
First Aid Safety PostersGeneral Safety Posters
Safety Signs & Labels
Fire Fighting Equipment Safety SignsGeneral Safety LabelsMandatory Safety SignsMulti-Purpose Safety SignsProhibition Safety SignsSafe Condition Safety SignsWarning Safety Signs
Security & Cctv Signs & Labels
Cctv Signs & LabelsGeneral Security SignsPublic Awareness SignsSecurity Notices
Vehicle & Traffic Signs
General Traffic SignsMirror SignsTraffic Sign AccessoriesRoad SignsVehicle Hazard MarkingBs873 Highway Approved SignsSchool trespass sign
Warehouse Identification Signs & Labels
Aisle & Bay MarkersDocument PocketsMagnetic & Self-Adhesive Label HoldersMagnetic Easy Wipe Racking TapeMagnetic Location MarkersMagnetic Self-Adhesive StripNumbers & LettersWarehouse Floor SignalsWeight Load Notices
Way guidance tapesClearanceNew Signs & Labels ProductsSigns & Labels Clearance
Storage & Shelving
Bulk Storage
AccessoriesDisplay Bins & ContainersDrums & KegsIBCsHand toolsPlastic Storage Containers
Containers & Tote Pans
Attached Lid ContainersDolliesFolding ContainersNesting ContainersStacking ContainersTote Pans & RacksTransit ContainersWire Containers & Baskets
Cupboards
Plastic CupboardsStainless Steel CupboardsSteel Cupboards
Cylinder Storage
Cylinder CagesCylinder Pallets & Racks
Drum Storage
Drum & IBC Storage UnitsDrum & Small Can RackingDrum Filling PointsSump FlooringSump Pallets
Pallets
Box PalletsFlat PalletsPallet Accessories
Racking
Cantilever RackingPallet RackingRacking ProtectionSheet RackingTyre RackingWide Span RackingRacking accessories
Sheds & Outdoor StorageMetro
Shelving
Aluminium ShelvingGalvanised & Zinc Plated Steel ShelvingPainted Steel ShelvingPlastic ShelvingStainless Steel ShelvingWire Shelving
Small Parts Storage
Louvered Panels & BinsSmall Parts ContainersSmall Parts Pigeon HolesSmall Parts ShelvingTray & Drawer Systems
New Storage & Shelving Products
Wheels & Castors
Castors
Cast Iron TyredNylon TyredPneumatic TyredPolypropylene TyredPolyurethane TyredSolid Rubber TyredThermoplastic Tyred
Wheel & Castor AccessoriesWheels
Cast Iron TyredNylon TyredPneumatic TyredPolyurethane TyredSolid Rubber TyredThermoplastictyred
New Wheels & Castors ProductsWheels & Castors ClearanceClearance
Workshop & Maintenance
Cable TyingCable & Hose
Cabling ProductsHose Products
Cleaners & degreasersDrain MaintenanceExtractorsFloor MaintenanceIndustrial Fans & BlowersGarage & Vehicle
Air CompressorsCleaning TanksCreepers & SeatingLifting EquipmentGenerators & starters
Grounds Maintenance
Bags Composters & Water SystemsBarrows & TrailersGrounds Maintenance Hand Tools
Lighting
BulbsDesk LightingTorches & Inspection LampsWorklights
Machinery
Welding Equipment
Measurement
Distance MeasurersElectrical TestingEndoscopes & MicroscopesEnvironmental MeasuringTimers & CountersWeighing ScalesPressure Meters
Oil fluids & lubricants
Power Supply
110 Volt Power Supply240 Volt Power Supply
Seating
ChairsStoolsSeating accessories
Tool Storage
Portable Tool StorageTool BoardsTool ChestsCupboards & Cabinets
Tools
HandtoolsPowertools
Workshop Trolleys
Open TrolleysStorage Trolleys
Workbenches
Steel WorkbenchesTimber Workbenches
Workstands & Workstations
WorkstandsWorkstations
Workshop & Maintenance ClearanceNew Workshop & Maintenance ProductsClearance
0 £0.00
UKROI
View/Request a Catalogue Today
Sign In / Register
My Account
My Basket (0) £0.00
You don't have any items in your Shopping Basket.
Quick Quote
Quick Shop
Catalogue Request
Our Products
Keyword
{{{name}}}
Category
{{{name}}}
24/7 Freephone: 0800 294 4440
Ladders & StepsWaste & RecyclingFlooring & MattingHandling & LiftingCleaning & HygieneMailroom & PackagingOfficePremisesLockers & CloakroomSafety & SecurityPPE & WorkwearSigns & LabelsStorage & ShelvingWheels & CastorsWorkshop & Maintenance
£ Price Challenge
FREE Delivery on orders over £40*
Export Division
HomePrivacy Policy
General Health & Safety Advise
Investor relations
Quality & Environment
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Website Data Protection and Privacy Statement
1.           GENERAL
HC Slingsby PLC together with any group companies (“we” “us” “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. For the purposes of data protection legislation, we are the data controller and we will process your personal data in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 and national laws which relate to the processing of personal data. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
2.           VISITORS TO OUR WEBSITE
2.1         We may collect and process personal data about you in the following circumstances:
2.1.1            when you complete forms on our website (“Site”). This includes your email address, name, contact telephone number, address, which is provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our services, requesting further services;
2.1.2            whenever you provide information to us when reporting a problem with our Site, making a complaint, making an enquiry or contacting us for any other reason. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
2.1.3            details of your visits to our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise, and the resources that you access (see section 2.2.2 on Cookies below); and
2.1.4            whenever you disclose your information to us, or we collect information from you in any other way, through our Site.
2.2         We may also collect data in the following ways:
IP Address
2.2.1            We may collect information about your device, including where available your Internet Protocol address, for reasons of fraud protection. We may also collect information about your device’s operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
Cookies
2.2.2            Our Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy.
2.3         We may use your personal data for the legitimate interests of HC Slingsby PLC in order to:
2.3.1            provide you with information, or services that you requested from us;
2.3.2            allow you to participate in interactive features of our Site, when you choose to do so;
2.3.3            ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device;
2.3.4            improve our Site and services;
2.3.5            process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by you; and
2.3.6            contact you for marketing purposes where you have signed up for these (see section 6 for further details).
Website Links
Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of third parties. Please note that if you follow a link to any of these websites, such websites will apply different terms to the collection and privacy of your personal data and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check before you submit your information to these websites.
3.           CUSTOMERS
3.1         We will collect details such as your email address, name, contact telephone number, address, bank details when you order goods or services from us either via our Site, by email, facsimile, post, electronic data links, by telephone (we may also record the conversation), if you complete an order/transaction form or send us a purchase order. We will use this information to process your order and comply with our contractual obligations.
3.2         In order to perform our contact with you, we may also need to share personal data with third parties such as payment providers, sub-contractors, suppliers, hauliers and postal service organisations to assist in the delivery of goods or services you have ordered;
3.3         We may also advertise your feedback on our website and marketing materials (subject to obtaining your prior consent where necessary);
3.4         We will retain your information as long as we require this to provide you with the goods or services ordered from us and for a period of 7 years afterwards. Where you have subscribed to receive marketing correspondence from us we will keep personal data 7 years from when you are provided with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing correspondence from us.
4.           SUPPLIERS
We will collect details such as email address, name, contact telephone number, address, bank details in order to contact you about goods or services ordered with you and to place further orders. We will keep the personal data for 7 years further to being provided with the goods/services.
5.           MARKETING
5.1         In addition to the uses described in sections 3-4 above, we may use Customer personal data for our legitimate interests in order to provide you with details about our goods, services, business updates and events which we think may be of interest.
5.2         If you are not an existing Customer but you invite us to provide information about our goods/services, we may collect your email address, name, contact telephone number and address for the purposes of providing you with information about our goods and services or offers.  We will retain such data for a period of 3 years from the point at which you provide us with your data, unless you place an order with us in which case 3.4 above will apply.
5.3         You have the right to opt-out of receiving the information detailed in section 5.1 at any time. To opt-out of receiving such information you can:
5.3.1            tick the relevant box situated in the form on which we collect your information or by logging into your account;
5.3.2            clicking the unsubscribe button contained in any such communication received; or
5.3.3            email us at mail-preferences@slingsby.com providing us with your name and contact details.
6.           AUTOMATED PROCESSING
6.1         We may use information regarding past purchasing patterns and your type of business in order for us to tailor our marketing material to your specific behaviour and activities (eg such as your previous use of handling equipment).  We use email monitoring services to monitor the emails which we send to users.  In doing this we obtain information such as but not limited to:
·         Time of receipt
·         Time of opening
·         Device user opened with
·         Location it was opened in
·         Which parts of the email you interacted with.
6.2         We use systems that enable us to link your social media accounts to your account if registered with the same email address.  This enables us to tailor our promotions and products as best as possible.
6.3         Where you have provided us with a mobile number we may market to you using SMS and Push notification interactions.
6.4         Our systems are set up to enable us to record your purchasing history with us and your market sector.  We link this data to your account so that we can determine what offers or informational emails or mailings may be of interest to you.
7.           LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA
7.1         In accordance with data protection legislation we are required to notify you of the legal basis upon which we process your personal data. We process your personal data for the following reasons:
7.1.1            for performance of a contract we enter into with you;
7.1.2            where necessary for compliance with a legal obligation we are subject to; and
7.1.3            for our legitimate interests (as described within this policy).
8.           DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA to third parties
8.1         We may disclose your information to third parties for the following legitimate interests:
8.1.1            to staff members, suppliers, contractors and hauliers in order to facilitate the provision of goods, services or product information to you;
8.1.2            to our affiliated entities to support internal administration;
8.1.3            IT software providers that host our website and store data on our behalf; and
8.1.4            to a prospective buyer of some or all of our business or assets, in which case personal data including personal data will also be one of the transferred assets.
8.2         We may disclose personal data to the police, regulatory bodies, legal advisors or similar third parties where we are under a legal duty to disclose or share personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, or safety of our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
8.3         We will not sell or distribute personal data to other organisations without your approval.
9.           CROSS-BORDER DATA TRANSFERS
9.1         We will not transfer your personal data outside the European Economic Area.
10.        DATA SECURITY
10.1       Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
10.2       Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk.
10.3       Information you provide to us is shared on our secure servers. We have implemented appropriate physical, technical and organisational measures designed to secure your information against accidental loss and unauthorised access, use, alteration or disclosure. In addition, we limit access to personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties that have a legitimate business need for such access.
11.        ACCESS TO, UPDATING, DELETING AND RESTRICTING USE OF PERSONAL DATA
11.1       It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current.  Please keep us informed if the personal data we hold about you changes.
11.2       Data protection legislation gives you the right to object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances or withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data where this has been provided. You also have the right to access information held about you and for this to be provided in an intelligible form. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send an email to dataprotection@slingsby.com.  In certain circumstances we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee to comply with your request.
11.3       You can also ask us to undertake the following:
11.3.1         update or amend your personal data if you feel this is inaccurate;
11.3.2         remove your personal data from our database entirely;
11.3.3         send you copies of your personal data in a commonly used format and transfer your information to another entity where you have supplied this to us, and we process this electronically with your consent or where necessary for the performance of a contract; or
11.3.4         restrict the use of your personal data.
11.4       We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and your right to access, and to provide you with the personal data that we hold about you or make your requested changes. Data protection legislation may allow or require us to refuse to provide you with access to some or all the personal data that we hold about you or to comply with any requests made in accordance with your rights referred to above. If we cannot provide you with access to your personal data, or process any other request we receive, we will inform you of the reasons why, subject to any legal or regulatory restrictions.
11.5       Please send any requests relating to the above to our Data Lead at dataprotection@slingsby.com specifying your name and the action you would like us to undertake.
12.        RIGHT TO WITHDRAW CONSENT
Where you have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal data, you have the legal right to withdraw your consent under certain circumstances. To withdraw your consent, if applicable, please contact us at dataprotection@slingsby.com.
13.        CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to update this privacy policy at any time, and any changes we make to our privacy policy will be posted on this page. We will notify you if there are any changes to this policy that materially affect how we collect, store or process your personal data. If we would like to use your previously collected personal data for different purposes than those we notified you about at the time of collection, we will provide you with notice and, where required by law, seek your consent, before using your personal data for a new or unrelated purpose. We may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent where required by applicable law or regulation.
14.        CONTACT US
We have appointed a Data Lead to oversee compliance with this privacy policy. If you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this policy or how we use your personal data please contact our Data Lead at dataprotection@slingsby.com. This is in addition to your right to contact the Information Commissioners Office if you are unsatisfied with our response to any issues you raise at https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/
Last updated: April 2018.
At Slingsby we offer Industrial & Commercial Equipment
With FREE Next Day Delivery* on all stock lines.
The right products at the right price
Delivery when you want it
Friendly technical support
12 months warranty
